<?xml-model type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<doc name = "Library Catalog">
<locA> 
	<AM> 
		<ref>AM 111 .G8 - The Management of Small History Museums, Carl E. Guthe</ref>
		<ref>AM 151 .N37 - Exhibits for the Small Museum: A Handbook, Arminta Neal</ref>
  		<ref>AM 1 .A533 no. 17 - So You Want a Good Museum: A Guide to the Management of Small Museums, Carl E. Guthe</ref>
  		<ref>AM 1 .A533 no. 17 c.2 - So You Want a Good Museum: A Guide to the Management of Small Museums, Carl E. Guthe</ref> 
  		<ref>AM 7 .E9 2008 - Excellence and Equity: Education and the Public Dimension of Museums, The American Association of Museums</ref> 
  		<ref>AM 7 .R56 - Museums and Related Institutions: A Basic Program Survey, Lola Eriksen Rogers</ref>
  		<ref>AM 7 .M37 2002 - Mastering Civic Engagement: A Challenge to Museums, The American Association of Museums</ref>
  		<ref>AM 11 .A63 2008 - National Standards and Best Practices for U.S. Museums, The American Association of Museums</ref>
  		<ref>AM 11 .U87 1994 - Guidelines for Museums, Beatriee S. Utley and Charlene Perkins Cutler</ref>
  		<ref>AM 121 .M877 2007 - Museum Management and Marketing, ed. Richard Sandell and Robert R. Janes</ref>
  		<ref>AM 122 .S58 2003 - Slaying the Financial Dragon: Strategies for Museums, The American Association of Museums</ref>
  		<ref>AM 124 .B6 1999 - Introduction to Museum Evaluation, ed. Minda Borun and Randi Korn</ref> 
  		<ref>AM 139 .C493 1988 - The Revised Nomenclature for Museum Cataloging, James R. Blackaby and Patricia Greeno</ref>
  		<ref>AM 139 .P37 2004 - PastPerfect Museum Software Version 4.0 User’s Guide, Mary Parr, Richard Hilton, and James Danner</ref> 
	</AM>
</locA>

<locB>
	<BR>
		<ref>BR 520 .M36 1982 - Radical Sects of Revolutionary New England, Stephen A. Marini</ref>
	</BR>
</locB>

<locC>
	<CC>
		<ref>CC 77 .H3 - Archeology and the Historical Society, J.C. Harrington</ref>
	</CC>
	<CS>
		<ref>CS 71 .B87 1932 - My Great Grandfather’s House in Exeter New Hampshire, James Emery Brooks</ref>
		<ref>CS 71 .L948 - Ludwig Genealogy, M.R. Ludwig</ref>
	</CS>
	<CT>
		<ref>CT 238 .S76 2006 - Eminent Mainers: Succinct Biographies of Thousands of Amazing Mainers, Mostly Dead, and a Few People from Away Who Have Done Something Useful Within the State of Maine, Arthur Douglas Stover </ref>
		<ref>CT 275 .B78483 Z58 - Giving it All Away: The Doris Buffett Story, Michael Zitz</ref>
	</CT>

<locD>
	<D>
		<ref>D 13 .A5 - Local History Contributions and Techniques in the Study of Two Colonial Cities, The American Association for State and Local History</ref>
		<ref>D 16.2 .W56 2001 - Historical Thinking and Other Unnatural Acts: Charting the Future of Teaching the Past, Sam Wineburg</ref>
		<ref>D 16.255 .C65 M39 2005 - The AHA guide to Teaching and Learning with New Media, John McClymer</ref>
	</D>
	<DA>
		<ref>DA 688 .F57 2010 - When London was Capital of America, Julie Flavell</ref>
	<DA>
	<DC
		<ref>DC 755 .G6 - Les Victimes De Picpus 1794-1994</ref>
	<DC>

		
