<?xml-model type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<doc name = "Library Catalog">
<locA> 
	<AM> 
		<ref>AM 111 .G8 - The Management of Small History Museums, Carl E. Guthe</ref>
		<ref>AM 151 .N37 - Exhibits for the Small Museum: A Handbook, Arminta Neal</ref>
  		<ref>AM 1 .A533 no. 17 - So You Want a Good Museum: A Guide to the Management of Small Museums, Carl E. Guthe</ref>
  		<ref>AM 1 .A533 no. 17 c.2 - So You Want a Good Museum: A Guide to the Management of Small Museums, Carl E. Guthe</ref> 
  		<ref>AM 7 .E9 2008 - Excellence and Equity: Education and the Public Dimension of Museums, The American Association of Museums</ref> 
  		<ref>AM 7 .R56 - Museums and Related Institutions: A Basic Program Survey, Lola Eriksen Rogers</ref>
  		<ref>AM 7 .M37 2002 - Mastering Civic Engagement: A Challenge to Museums, The American Association of Museums</ref>
  		<ref>AM 11 .A63 2008 - National Standards and Best Practices for U.S. Museums, The American Association of Museums</ref>
  		<ref>AM 11 .U87 1994 - Guidelines for Museums, Beatriee S. Utley and Charlene Perkins Cutler</ref>
  		<ref>AM 121 .M877 2007 - Museum Management and Marketing, ed. Richard Sandell and Robert R. Janes</ref>
  		<ref>AM 122 .S58 2003 - Slaying the Financial Dragon: Strategies for Museums, The American Association of Museums</ref>
  		<ref>AM 124 .B6 1999 - Introduction to Museum Evaluation, ed. Minda Borun and Randi Korn</ref> 
  		<ref>AM 139 .C493 1988 - The Revised Nomenclature for Museum Cataloging, James R. Blackaby and Patricia Greeno</ref>
  		<ref>AM 139 .P37 2004 - PastPerfect Museum Software Version 4.0 User’s Guide, Mary Parr, Richard Hilton, and James Danner</ref> 
	</AM>
</locA>

<locB>
	<BR>
		<ref>BR 520 .M36 1982 - Radical Sects of Revolutionary New England, Stephen A. Marini</ref>
	</BR>
</locB>

<locC>
	<CC>
		<ref>CC 77 .H3 - Archeology and the Historical Society, J.C. Harrington</ref>
	</CC>
	<CS>
		<ref>CS 71 .B87 1932 - My Great Grandfather’s House in Exeter New Hampshire, James Emery Brooks</ref>
		<ref>CS 71 .L948 - Ludwig Genealogy, M.R. Ludwig</ref>
	</CS>
	<CT>
		<ref>CT 238 .S76 2006 - Eminent Mainers: Succinct Biographies of Thousands of Amazing Mainers, Mostly Dead, and a Few People from Away Who Have Done Something Useful Within the State of Maine, Arthur Douglas Stover </ref>
		<ref>CT 275 .B78483 Z58 - Giving it All Away: The Doris Buffett Story, Michael Zitz</ref>
	</CT>

<locD>
	<D>
		<ref>D 13 .A5 - Local History Contributions and Techniques in the Study of Two Colonial Cities, The American Association for State and Local History</ref>
		<ref>D 16.2 .W56 2001 - Historical Thinking and Other Unnatural Acts: Charting the Future of Teaching the Past, Sam Wineburg</ref>
		<ref>D 16.255 .C65 M39 2005 - The AHA guide to Teaching and Learning with New Media, John McClymer</ref>
	</D>
	<DA>
		<ref>DA 688 .F57 2010 - When London was Capital of America, Julie Flavell</ref>
	<DA>
	<DC
		<ref>DC 755 .G6 - Les Victimes De Picpus 1794-1994</ref>
	<DC>

<locE>
	<E>
		<ref>E 46 .K45 2007 - Jamestown, Quebec, Santa Fe: Three North American Beginnings, James C. Kelly and Barbara Clark Smith</ref>
		<ref>E 59 .F53 E53 2000 - Encounters in the New World: A History in Documents, Jill Lepore</ref>
		<ref>E 77 .A4963 2009 - American Indian History: A Documentary Reader, ed. Camilla Townsend</ref> 
		<ref>E 78 .M2 R65 2004 - Unsettled Past, Unsettled Future: The Story of Maine Indians, Neil Rolde</ref> 
		<ref>E 78 .M2 R65 2004 c.2 - Unsettled Past, Unsettled Future: The Story of Maine Indians, Neil Rolde</ref>
		<ref>E 78 .N5 R87 - Indian New England Before the Mayflower, Howard S. Russell</ref> 
		<ref>E 83.67 .L46 - The Name of War: King Philip’s War and the Origins of American Identity, Jill Lepore</ref> 
		<ref>E 83.775 .C355 2007 - The Shawnees and the War for America, Collin G. Calloway</ref>
		<ref>E 99 .A13 W33 1989 - The Wabanakis of Maine and the Maritimes: A Resource Book about Penobscot. Passamaquoddy, Maliseet, Micmac and Abenaki Indians, The American Friends Service Committee</ref> 
		<ref>E 99 .O45 G54 2006 - Forgotten Allies: The Oneida Indians and the American Revolution, Joseph T. Galtthaar and James Kirby Martin</ref> 
		<ref>E 129 .W3 M2 - Waymough Terrentenary: An Account of the Celebration of the Landing of George Waymough on the Coast of Maine</ref> 
		<ref>E 151 .H5 vol. 10 no. 1 - Historic Preservation, The National Trust for Historic Preservation</ref> 
		<ref>E 159 .H265 2007 - New Solutions for House Museums: Ensuring the Long-Term Preservation of America’s Historic Houses, Donna Ann Harris</ref> 
		<ref>E 159 .L33 2006 - Where we Lived: Discovering the Paces we Once Called Home, the American Home from 1775-1840, Jack Larkin</ref> 
		<ref>E 159 .T24 1990 - Historic Homes of America, James Tackach</ref> 
		<ref>E 160 .U614 - Glimpses of Historic Areas East of the Mississippi River, The National Park Service</ref> 
		<ref>E 161 .M36 1988 - Material Life in America 1600-1860, ed. Robert Blair St. George</ref> 
		<ref>E 162 .C33 1997 - Colonial Kids: An Activity Guide to Life in the New World, Laurie Carlson</ref> 
		<ref>E 162 .D46 2004 - Circles and Lines: The Shape of Life in Early America, John Demos</ref> 
		<ref>E 162 .D46 2004 c.2 - Circles and Lines: The Shape of Life in Early America, John Demos</ref> 
		<ref>E 163 .G35 2002 - America’s Founding Secret: What the Scottish Enlightenment Taught our Founding Fathers, Robert W. Galvin</ref> 
		<ref>E 164 .E4 1979 - After the Revolution: Profiles of Early American Culture, Joseph J. Ellis</ref> 
		<ref>E 164 .L26 1988 - The Reshaping of Everyday Life 1790-1840, Jack Larkin</ref> 
		<ref>E 164 .W63 2009 - Empire of Liberty: A history of the Early Republic, 1789-1815, Gordon S. Wood</ref> 
		<ref>E 169.1 .F539 E 162 1989 vol. 1 - Albion’s Seed: Four British Folkways in America, David Hackett Fischer</ref> 
		<ref>E 171 .A64 1966 - American Heritage, The American Association for State and Local History</ref> 
		<ref>E 171 .A64 1969 - American Heritage, The American Association for State and Local History</ref> 
		<ref>E 171 .M96 - My Country, My Country Society</ref> 
		<ref>E 173 .O94 2005 - The Glorious Cause: The American Revolution, 1763-1789, Robert Middlekauff</ref> 
		<ref>E 173 .P77 204 - Posterity: Letters of Great Americans to Their Children, Dorrie McCullough Lawson</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.1 - Encyclopedia of American History: Beginnings to 1607, ed. Peter C. Mancall</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.2 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1608 1760, ed. Billy G. Smith</ref>
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.3 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1761-1812, ed. Paul A. Gilje</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.4 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1813-1855, ed. Malcolm J. Rohrbough</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.5 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1856-1869, ed. Joan Waugh</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.6 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1870-1899, ed. Ari Hoogenboom</ref>
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.7 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1900-1928, ed. Elizabeth Faue</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.8 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1929-1945, ed. John W. Jeffries</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.9 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1946-1968, ed. Allan M. Winkler</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.10 - Encyclopedia of American History: 1969 to the Present, ed. Donald T. Critchlow</ref>
		<ref>E 174 .E54 2003 vol.11 - Encyclopedia of American History: Index, Facts on File Library of American History</ref> 
		<ref>E 174 .R43 1991 - The Reader’s Companion to American History, ed. Eric Foner and John A. Garraty</ref> 
		<ref>E 174.5 .A45 - The Almanac of American History, ed. Arthur M. Schlesinger, Jr.</ref> 
		<ref>E 174.5 .N47 2003 - The New York Public Library American History Desk Reference: The Definitive Source for Answers to All Your Questions on American History, ed. Sarah Parvis</ref> 
		<ref>E 175.8 .S37 2007 - Eyewitness to the Past: Strategies for teaching American History in Grades 5-12, Joan Brodkey Schur</ref>
		<ref>E 176 .H866 2007 - Houses of the Founding Fathers, Hugh Howard and Roger Straus III</ref>
		<ref>E 176 .R63 2004 - Founding Mothers: The Women Who Raised our Nation, Cokie Roberts</ref> 
		<ref>E 176 .R63 2004 c.2- Founding Mothers: The Women Who Raised our Nation, Cokie Roberts</ref> 
		<ref>E 176 .R634 2008 - Ladies of Liberty: The Women Who Shaped Our Nation, Cokie Roberts</ref> 
		<ref>E 178 .B46 2006 - America: the Last Best Hope, William J. Bennett</ref> 
		<ref>E 178 .Z75 2003 - A People’s History of the United States, Howard Zinn</ref> 
		<ref>E 185.25 .D37 2003 - Don’t Know Much About History: Everything You Need to Know About American History but Never Learned, Kenneth C. Davis</ref> 
		<ref>E 178.3 - .S735 2007 - A Young People’s History of the United States, Howard Zinn, adapted by Rebecca Stefoff</ref>
		<ref>E 178.6 .B645 2002 - Booknotes: Stories from American History, Brian Lamb </ref>
		<ref>E 178.6 .S46 1991 - “I Love Paul Revere, Whether He Rode or Not”, Richard Shenkman</ref> 
		<ref>E 178.6 .S46 1991 c.2 - “I Love Paul Revere, Whether He Rode or Not”, Richard Shenkman</ref>
		<ref>E 178.6 .S47 - Legends, Lies, and Cherished Myths of American History, Richard Shenkman</ref> 
		<ref>E 178.6 .S47 c.2 - Legends, Lies, and Cherished Myths of American History, Richard Shenkman</ref>
		<ref>E 178.6 .S473 2003 - One-Night Stands with American History: Odd, Amusing, and Little-Known Incidents, Richard Shenkman and Kurt Reiger</ref> 
		<ref>E 181 .T85 2006 - Don Troiani’s American Battles: The Art of the Nation at War, 1754-1865, Robert K. Krick, Keith Knoke, Lee White, Robert E. L. Krick, Dr. Richard Sauers, James L. Kochan, Bob McDonald, Jay Jorgensen, Dr. David Evans, and Brian Pohanka</ref> 
		<ref>E 182 .P466 - “Old Bruin”: Commodore Matthew Calbraith Perry, Samuel Eliot Morison</ref> 
		<ref>E 183.7 .S373 1986 - The Cycles of American History, Arthur M. Schlesinger, Jr.</ref> 
		<ref>E 183 .F8 M13 - America and France: The Historic Ties That Bind, David McCullough</ref>
		<ref>E 184.6 .P36 2001 - Pamphlets of Protest: An Anthology of Early African American Protest Literature, 1790-1860, ed. Richard Newman, Patrick Rael, and Philip Lapsansky</ref> 
		<ref>E 185.917 .P54 1988 - Black Yankees: The Development of an Afro-American Subculture in Eighteenth-Century New England, William D. Piersen</ref> 
		<ref>E 195.93 .M15 P75 2006 - Maine’s visible Black History: The First Chronicle of Its People, H.H. Price and Gerald E. Talbot</ref> 
		<ref>E 187 .G73 2003 - Colonial America, Edward Gray</ref> 
		<ref>E 188 .E63 1989 - The Encyclopedia of Colonial and Revolutionary America, John Mack Faragher</ref>  
		<ref>E 188.5 .M67 2004 - The Genuine Article, Edmund S. Morgan</ref> 
		<ref>E 199 .P39 - Fort Ticonderoga, S. H. P. Pell</ref> 
		<ref>E 202.1 .A129 - Annual Report of the Society of the Cincinnati: 2009, The Society of the Cincinnati</ref>
		<ref>E 202.1 .A7 M93 1983 - Liberty Without Anarchy: A History of the Society of the Cincinnati, Minor Myers Jr.</ref> 
		<ref>E 202.1 .A7 T43 - The Society of the Cincinnati, 1783-1935, William S. Thomas</ref> 
		<ref>E 202.1 .A7 W28 - the Society of the Cincinnati, The Massachusetts Society of the Cincinnati</ref> 
		<ref>E 202.1 .A7 W28 c.2 - the Society of the Cincinnati, The Massachusetts Society of the Cincinnati</ref> 
		<ref>E 202.1 .N3 no. 7 - The Society of the Cincinnati in New Hampshire, Foster Stearns</ref> 
		<ref>E 202.1 .V346 1938 - Papers of the Society of the Cincinnati in the State of Virginia 1783-1824, ed. Edgar Erskine Hume</ref> 
		<ref>E 202.3 .A5 S66 1982 - Handbook of the National Society of the Sons of the American Revolution, The Sons of the American Revolution</ref>
		<ref>E 202.5 .A19 B35 2007 - American Treasure: the Enduring Spirit of the DAR, Biana L. Bailey</ref> 
		<ref>E 202.5 .A7 H86 1991 - A Century of Service: The Story of the DAR, Ann Arnold Hunter</ref>
		<ref>E 202.5 .M24 - Maine Society Daughters of the American Revolution Roster and Ancestral Roll, 1948, Mrs. Percy L. Tate</ref> 
		<ref>E 206 .G46 1994 - George Washington’s Generals and Opponents, ed. George Athan Billias</ref> 
		<ref>E 206 .J92 - The Sages and Heroes of the American Revolution in Two Parts, L. Caroll Judson</ref>
		<ref>E 207 .G9 M54 2007 - Nathanael Greene: The General Who Saved the Revolution, Gregg A. Mierka</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K4 F6 1931 - General Knox and his Home in Maine: Montpelier, Henry Thatcher Fowler</ref>
		<ref>E 207 .K4 F6 1931 c.2 - General Knox and his Home in Maine: Montpelier, Henry Thatcher Fowler</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K4 F6 1931 c.3 - General Knox and his Home in Maine: Montpelier, Henry Thatcher Fowler</ref>
		<ref>E 207 .K74 A6 - An Appeal to Make Montpelier the Home of Major General Henry Knox at Thomaston, Maine a National Shrine</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 A6 c.2 - An Appeal to Make Montpelier the Home of Major General Henry Knox at Thomaston, Maine a National Shrine</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 A6 c.3 - An Appeal to Make Montpelier the Home of Major General Henry Knox at Thomaston, Maine a National Shrine</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 A6 c.4 - An Appeal to Make Montpelier the Home of Major General Henry Knox at Thomaston, Maine a National Shrine</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 A6 c.5 - An Appeal to Make Montpelier the Home of Major General Henry Knox at Thomaston, Maine a National Shrine</ref>
		<ref>E 207 .K74 B65 - Ye Cohorn Caravan, Wm. L. Bowne</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 B65 c.2 - Ye Cohorn Caravan, Wm. L. Bowne</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 B8 1900 - Henry Knox, Noah Brooks</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 C18 - Henry Knox: General Washington's General, North Callahan</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 C18 c.2 - Henry Knox: General Washington's General, North Callahan</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 C18 c.3 - Henry Knox: General Washington's General, North Callahan</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 C18 c.4 - Henry Knox: General Washington's General, North Callahan</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 G7 - Major General Henry Knox and the Last Heirs to Montpelier, Thomas Morgan Griffiths</ref>
		<ref>E 207 .K74 H14 - 1776: Washington’s First Victory, E. H. Haines</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 M7 - Unending Passions: The Knox Letters, Pamela Murrow</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 S56 2010 - Henry Knox: Bookseller, Soldier, Patriot, Anita Silvey</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 S7 - General Henry Knox and his Family, his Manor, his Manor House, and his Guests (1902), Lewis Frederick Starrett</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .K74 S77 2007 - Henry Knox: Washington’s Artilleryman, Richard M. Strum</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .L2 L68 - Emblem of Liberty, Anne C. Loveland</ref>
		<ref>E 207 .M76 D9 2004 - Collections Catalogue of the General Henry Knox Museum, Ellen S. Dyler</ref>
		<ref>E 207 .M76 D9 2004 c.2 - Collections Catalogue of the General Henry Knox Museum, Ellen S. Dyler</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .M76 D9 2004 c.3 - Collections Catalogue of the General Henry Knox Museum, Ellen S. Dyler</ref> 
		<ref>E 207 .T13 F69 1995 - Silas Talbot: Captain of Old Ironsides, William M. Fowler, Jr.</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .L23 1984 - The American Heritage History of the American Revolution, Bruce Lancaster</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .L23 1984 c.2 - The American Heritage History of the American Revolution, Bruce Lancaster</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .M12 c.2 - The Revolutionary War, Bart McDowell</ref>
		<ref>E 208 .M393 2005 - 1776, David McCullough</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .M393 2005 c.2 - 1776, David McCullough</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .M393 2005 c.3 - 1776, David McCullough</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .M3963 2007 - 1776 (the Illustrated Edition), David McCullough</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .M534 2006 - Yankee Doodle America, Wendell Minor</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .M83 1997 - If you Lived at the Time of the American Revolution, Kay Moore</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .M85 1956 - The Birth of the Republic, Edmund S. Morgan</ref> 
		<ref>E 208 .N33 2005 - The Unknown American Revolution, Gary B. Nash</ref> 
		<ref>E 209 .J33 1973 - The American Revolution Considered as a Social Movement, J, Franklin Jameson</ref>
		<ref>E 209 .K58 2009 - Sensibility and the American Revolution, Sarah Knott</ref>
		<ref>E 209 .S33 2004 - George vs. George: The American Revolution as Seen From Both Sides, Rosalyn Schanzer</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .C73 2003 - The American Revolution, Edward Countryman</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .F3 M4 - The Federalist Era 1789-1801, John C. Miller</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .H686 2010 - Declaration: The Nine Tumultuous Weeks When America Became Independent, May 1-July 4, 1776, William Hogeland</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .P64 - One Nation Under God, Ralph J. Pollard</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .S88 2006 - Causes of the American Revolution, Richard M. Strum</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .S88 2006 c.2 - Causes of the American Revolution, Richard M. Strum</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .S88 2006 c.3 - Causes of the American Revolution, Richard M. Strum</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .S88 2006 c.4 - Causes of the American Revolution, Richard M. Strum</ref> 
		<ref>E 210 .T83 1982 - The Fall of the First British Empire, Robert W. Tucker and David C. Hendrickson</ref> 
		<ref>E 215.2 .M57 - Prologue to Revolution: Sources and Documents on the Stamp Act Crisis, 1764-1766, Edmund S. Morgan</ref> 
		<ref>E 215.4 Z7 - The Boston Massacre, Hiller B. Zobel</ref> 
		<ref>E 230 .M34 2006 - A Respectable Army: The Military Origins of the Republic 1763-1789, James Kirby Martin and Mark Edward Lender</ref>
		<ref>E 230 .S435 2006 - A Guide to the Battles of the American Revolution, Theodore P. Savas and J. David Dameron</ref> 
		<ref>E 230 .S5 1990 - A People Numerous and Armed, John Shy</ref> 
		<ref>E 230 .S75 2007 - Patriot Battles: How the War of Independence was Fought, Michael Stephenson</ref> 
		<ref>E 232 .C5 1966 - The Tide Turns: An Informal History of the Campaign of 1776 in the American Revolution, Donald Barr Chidsey</ref> 
		<ref>E 234 .F58 - Washington’s Secret War, Thomas Fleming</ref> 
		<ref>E 234 .R36 - Valley Forge: Crucible of Victory, John F. Reed</ref>
		<ref>E 241 .M7 S5 - The Battle of Monmouth, Samuel Stelle Smith</ref> 
		<ref>E 241 .P8 Y47 - The burning of Falmouth: October 18, 1775, Donald A. Yerxa</ref> 
		<ref>E 241 .P9 S6 - The Battle of Princeton, Samuel Stelle Smith</ref> 
		<ref>E 241 .T7 B66 2009 - Trenton and Princeton 1776-77: Washington Crosses the Delaware, David Bonk</ref> 
		<ref>E 241 .T7 D88 1998 - The Day is Ours! An Inside view of the Battles of Trenton and Princeton, November 1776-January 1777, William M. Dwyer</ref> 
		<ref>E 241 .T7 S6 - The Battle of Trenton, Samuel Stelle Smith</ref> 
		<ref>E 241 .V14 N45 2006 - Benedict Arnold’s Navy: The Ragtag Fleet That Lost the Battle of Lake Champlain but Won the American Revolution, James L. Nelson</ref> 
		<ref>E 241 .V14 N45 2006 c.2 - Benedict Arnold’s Navy: The Ragtag Fleet That Lost the Battle of Lake Champlain but Won the American Revolution, James L. Nelson</ref> 
		<ref>E 249 .F55 2007 - The Perils of Peace: America’s Struggle for Survival After Yorktown, Thomas Fleming</ref> 
		<ref>E 249 .F60 2011 - La Route De l’Independance… de Versailles a Yorktown, Philippe Cenci</ref> 
		<ref>E 251 .T76 2007 - Don Troiani’s Soldiers of the American Revolution, James L. Kochan</ref> 
		<ref>E 259 .B83 2004 - The Road to Valley Forge: How Washington Built the Army that Won the Revolution, John Buchanan</ref> 
		<ref>E 259 .M67 2006 - How to be a Revolutionary War Soldier, Thomas Ratliff</ref> 
		<ref>E 259 .R69 - A Revolutionary People at War: The continental Army and American Character, 1775-1783, Charles Royster</ref> 
		<ref>E 259 .R69 c.2 - A Revolutionary People at War: The continental Army and American Character, 1775-1783, Charles Royster</ref> 
		<ref>E 259 .S43 1972 - The Continental Artillery in Winter Encampment at Pluckemin, New Jersey, December, 1778-June, 1779, Clifford Sekel Jr.</ref> 
		<ref>E 263 .M4 C 43 2010 - To Hazard Our Own Security: Maine’s Role in the American Revolution, Michael Cecere</ref> 
		<ref>E 265 .F65  - France and New England, Allan Forbes and Paul F. Cadman</ref>
		<ref>E 267 .P4 2000 - Those Damned Rebels: The American Revolution as Seen Through British Eyes, Michael Pearson</ref>
		<ref>E 267 .U73 2007 - Fusiliers: The Saga of a British Redcoat Regiment in the American Revolution, Mark Urban</ref> 
		<ref>E 271 .P27 2008 - Patriot Pirates, Robert H. Patton</ref> 
		<ref>E 275 .A2 R43 1987 - Rebels and Redcoats: The American Revolution Through the Eyes of Those Who Fought and Lived It, George F. Scheer and Hugh F. Rankin</ref> 
		<ref>E 275 .G2 - The Secret Soldier: The Story of Deborah Sampson, Ann McGovern</ref> 
		<ref>E 275 .M38 2008 - Ordinary Courage: The Revolutionary War Adventures of Joseph Plumb Martin, ed. James Kirby Martin</ref> 
		<ref>E 276 .B47 - Revolutionary Mothers: Women in the Struggle for America’s Independence, Carol Berkin</ref> 
		<ref>E 276 .G36 Y68 - Masquerade: The Life and Times of Deborah Sampson, Continental Soldier, Alfred F. Young</ref> 
		<ref>E 278 .A7 M37 1997 - Benedict Arnold Revolutionary Hero: An American Warrior Reconsidered, James Kirby Martin</ref> 
		<ref>E 278 .A7 M37 1997 c.2 - Benedict Arnold Revolutionary Hero: An American Warrior Reconsidered, James Kirby Martin</ref> 
		<ref>E 278 .A7 M37 1997 c.3 - Benedict Arnold Revolutionary Hero: An American Warrior Reconsidered, James Kirby Martin</ref> 
		<ref>E 281 .B87 2008 - Forgotten Patriots: The Untold Story of American Prisoners During the Revolutionary War, Edwin G. Burrows</ref> 
		<ref>E 283 .W54 1997 - Revolutionary Medicine 1700-1800, C. Keith Wilbur</ref> 
		<ref>E 302 .H2573 - Alexander Hamilton and the Founding of the Nation, ed. Richard B. Morris</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.5 .E45 2000 - Founding Brothers, Joseph J. Ellis</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.5 .E45 2000 c.2 - Founding Brothers, Joseph J. Ellis</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.5 .F54 2009 - The Intimate Lives of the Founding Fathers, Thomas Fleming</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.5 .G9 - Fathers of the Revolution, Philip Guedalla</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.6 .A2 P85 2006 - Samuel Adams: Father of the American Revolution, Mark Puls</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.6 .F8 I83 2003 - Benjamin Franklin: An American Life, Walter Isaacson</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.6 .F8 I83 2003 c.2 - Benjamin Franklin: An American Life, Walter Isaacson</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.6 .H2 B76 1999 - Alexander Hamilton, American, Richard Brookhiser</ref>
		<ref>E 302.6 .R77 M54 2010 - Betsy Ross and the Making of America, Marla R. Miller</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.6 .R77 M54 2010 c.2 - Betsy Ross and the Making of America, Marla R. Miller</ref> 
		<ref>E 302.6 .R77 M54 2010 c.3 - Betsy Ross and the Making of America, Marla R. Miller</ref> 
		<ref>E 303 .B47 2002 - A Brilliant Solution: Inventing the American Constitution, Carol Berkin</ref> 
		<ref>E 303 .B49 1987 - Beyond Confederation, ed. Richard Beeman, Stephen Botein and Edward C. Carter II</ref> 
		<ref>E 310.7 .V33 1983 - New England and Foreign Relations 1789-1850, Paul A. Varg</ref>
		<ref>E 312 .A58 1984 - George Washington: A Biography, John R. Alden</ref> 
		<ref>E 312 .H54 2006 - Realistic Visionary: A Portrait of George Washington, Peter R. Henriques</ref>
		<ref>E 312 .S385 2009 - George Washington and his Generals, Emily L. Schulz and Laura B. Simo</ref>
		<ref>E 312 .S385 2009 c.2 - George Washington and his Generals, Emily L. Schulz and Laura B. Simo</ref>
		<ref>E 312 .S735 - The Life of George Washington, Jared Sparks</ref>
		<ref>E 312 .U29 2006 - The Unexpected George Washington: His Private Life, Harlow Giles Unger</ref> 
		<ref>E 312 .W33 1972 - George Washington: A Biography in his own Words, ed. Ralph K. Andrist</ref>
		<ref>E 312.17 M47 2006 - A Son and His Adoptive Father: The Marquis de Lafayette and George Washington, Christine H. Messing, John B. Rudder, and Diana Windham Shaw</ref>
		<ref>E 312.19 .P97 - The Mother of Washington and her Times, Mrs. Roger A. Pryor</ref>
		<ref>E 312.25 .F94 - Washington: Commander in Chief, Thomas Goddard Frothingham</ref>
		<ref>E 312.5 .G28 1999 - Washington’s Gardens at Mount Vernon, Mac Griswold</ref> 
		<ref>E 312.5 .G28 1999 c.2 - Washington’s Gardens at Mount Vernon, Mac Griswold</ref>
		<ref>E 312.5 M68 2000 - George Washington's Mount Vernon Official Guidebook, The Mount Vernon Ladies’ Association</ref> 
		<ref>E 312.5 .M68 2000 c.2 - George Washington's Mount Vernon Official Guidebook, The Mount Vernon Ladies’ Association</ref> 
		<ref>E 312.6 .N462 1889 - Catalogue of the Loan Exhibition of Historical Portraits and Relics, Metropolitan Opera House, New York City</ref> 
		<ref>E 312.78 1988 - George Washington’s Rules of Civility and Decent Behavior in Company and Conversation, George Washington</ref> 
		<ref>E 312.79 .W317 1999 - The Quotable George Washington, ed. Stephen E. Lucas</ref> 
		<ref>E 315 .H64 2006 - The Whiskey Rebellion, William Hogeland</ref> 
		<ref>E 322 .M38 2001 - John Adams, David McCullough</ref> 
		<ref>E 332 .M25 1948 - Jefferson the Virginian, Dumas Malone</ref>
		<ref>E 332 .M25 vol.2 - Jefferson and the Rights of Man, Dumas Malone</ref> 
		<ref>E 332 .M25 vol.3 - Jefferson and the Ordeal of Liberty, Dumas Malone</ref> 
		<ref>E 332 .M25 vol.6 - Jefferson and His Time: The Sage of Monticello, Dumas Malone</ref> 
		<ref>E 332.1 .A38 H65 2009 - Abigail Adams: A Life, Woody Holton</ref> 
		<ref>E 332.1 .A38 H65 2009 c.2 - Abigail Adams: A Life, Woody Holton</ref> 
		<ref>E 340 .C5 A4 2002 - A Breach of Privilege: Cilley Family Letters 1820-1867, Eve Anderson</ref> 
		<ref>E 3421 .M2 A45 2006 - A Perfect Union: Dolley Madison and the Creation of the American Nation, Catherine Allgor</ref> 
		<ref>E 354 .H78 2012 - Mr. and Mrs. Madison’s War: America’s First Couple and the Second War of Independence, Hugh Howard </ref>
		<ref>E 449 .D75 D68 1996 - Narrative of the Life of Frederick Douglass, an American Slave, Written by Himself, ed. William L. Andrews and William S. McFeely </ref>
		<ref>E 449 .W564 2007 - Wilberforce, Lincoln, and the Abolition of Slavery: Sources in the History of Emancipation, ed. James G. Basker and Nicole A. Seary</ref> 
	</E>
</locE>

